const topicData = {
  analysis: {
    title: "Analysis",
    theory: "/data/Analysis/theorie.html",
    exercises: [
      {
        title: "Aufgabe 1",
        subexercises: [
          {
            question: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe1/1.html",
            solution: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe1/L1.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe1/2.html",
            solution: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe1/L2.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe1/3.html",
            solution: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe1/L3.html"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        title: "Aufgabe 2",
        subexercises: [
          {
            question: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe2/1.html",
            solution: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe2/L1.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe2/2.html",
            solution: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe2/L2.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe2/3.html",
            solution: "/data/Analysis/aufgabe2/L3.html"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  vektorgeometrie: {
    title: "Vektorgeometrie",
    theory: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/theorie.html",
    exercises: [
      {
        title: "Aufgabe 1",
        subexercises: [
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/1.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/L1.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/2.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/L2.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/3.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/L3.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/4.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/L4.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/5.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/L5.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/6.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe1/L6.html"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        title: "Aufgabe 2",
        subexercises: [
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe2/1.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe2/L1.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe2/2.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe2/L2.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe2/3.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe2/L3.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe2/4.html",
            solution: "/data/Vektorgeometrie/aufgabe2/L4.html"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  wahrscheinlichkeit: {
    title: "Wahrscheinlichskeitrechnung",
    theory: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/theorie.html",
    exercises: [
      {
        title: "Aufgabe 1",
        subexercises: [
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe1/1.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe1/L1.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe1/2.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe1/L2.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe1/3.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe1/L3.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe1/4.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe1/L4.html"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        title: "Aufgabe 2",
        subexercises: [
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe2/1.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe2/L1.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe2/2.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe2/L2.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe2/3.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe2/L3.html"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        title: "Aufgabe 3",
        subexercises: [
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/1.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/L1.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/2.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/L2.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/3.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/L3.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/4.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/L4.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/5.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/L5.html"
          },
          {
            question: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/6.html",
            solution: "/data/Wahrscheinlichkeit/aufgabe3/L6.html"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
};